{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of computer science with this quiz.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is RAM?",
      "answers": ["Memory", "CPU", "Cache"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is HTTP?",
      "answers": ["Protocol", "Server", "Router"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is CSS?",
      "answers": ["Styles", "Script", "Markup"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "CPU stands for?",
      "answers": ["Unit", "Core", "Logic"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a bug?",
      "answers": ["Error", "Fix", "Hack"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is SQL?",
      "answers": ["Query", "Script", "Object"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "HTML is a?",
      "answers": ["Markup", "Script", "Binary"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Main OS by Apple?",
      "answers": ["macOS", "iOS", "Linux"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is a loop?",
      "answers": ["for", "int", "char"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is binary?",
      "answers": ["1010", "1234", "9999"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Python is a?",
      "answers": ["Script", "Markup", "Query"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Git is for?",
      "answers": ["Version", "Build", "Deploy"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "JS is short for?",
      "answers": ["JavaScr", "JustSay", "JumpSys"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is API?",
      "answers": ["Access", "Packet", "Image"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "IDE is used for?",
      "answers": ["Coding", "Gaming", "Hacking"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is a type?",
      "answers": ["int", "var", "sum"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Linux is a?",
      "answers": ["Kernel", "App", "Patch"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is a DB?",
      "answers": ["MySQL", "Python", "Bash"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "URL means?",
      "answers": ["Locator", "Server", "Path"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "A bit is?",
      "answers": ["Binary", "Logic", "Code"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
